RG 005:029, Office of the Governor: Raymond E. Baldwin (1943-1946)
Connecticut State Library
Raymond E. Baldwin records
1943-1946
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. Governor (1943-1946: Baldwin)
44.25 cubic feet
Gov. Raymond E. Baldwin's correspondence, subject files, and war orders from his second administration.
RG005_029
Multiple
Biographical Note
Born: August 31, 1893, Rye, New York.
College: Wesleyan University, 1916; Yale Law School, 1921.
Political Party: Republican.
Offices: Stratford Town Court, Prosecutor, 1927-1930,
Stratford Town Court, Judge, 1931-1933,
Connecticut General Assembly, House, 1930-1935,
Governor of Connecticut, 1939-1941, 1943-1946,
US Senate, 1946-1949,
Associate Justice, Connecticut Supreme Court of Errors, 1949-1959,
Chief Justice, Connecticut Supreme Court of Errors, 1959-1963.
Died: October 4, 1986, Fairfield, Connecticut.
It had been more than 70 years since a Connecticut governor who was voted out of office successfully won it back at a later election. Beginning in 1938, Raymond Baldwin ran for the office in four consecutive elections and won three of them.
Although his ancestors had lived in Connecticut for many years, Baldwin was born just across the border in Rye, New York, the son of Lucian Earl and Sarah Emily (Tyler) Baldwin. The family moved to Middletown, Connecticut in 1901, where he attended Central Grammar School, graduated from Middletown High School in 1912, and graduated from Wesleyan University in 1916. He served in the US Navy during World War I, enlisting as a seaman. He was assigned to officer training school and in February 1918 was commissioned as an ensign at Annapolis. His war service was on a destroyer. Following the war, he received a law degree from Yale in 1921. Baldwin practiced law in New Haven and Bridgeport. On June 29, 1922 he married Edith Lindholm of Middletown, daughter of Andrew and Louisa Lindholm, a graduate of Connecticut College at New London and a teacher at Middletown High School. They had three children. Edith died in 1970.
In 1922, Baldwin was interviewed by Republican Party chairman, J. Henry Roraback, who designated him to be Governor Templeton's personal secretary. However, Baldwin angered the party boss by refusing to do so. He served as prosecutor of the Stratford Town Court from 1927-1930 and judge of the Stratford Town Court from 1931-1933. In 1930 he was elected to the General Assembly; in 1933 he became House Majority Leader and chairman of the Judiciary Committee.
When Roraback committed suicide in 1937, the Republican Party had no one who was able to replace him as the party's boss. Baldwin collaborated with others in the party who called themselves "New Republicans" and was nominated to run for governor as a reform candidate. His campaign was aided by the strong vote gained that year by the Socialist candidate, Jasper McLevy. Baldwin was also helped by the Union Party, a small third party that made him its candidate for governor. This party's 3,046 votes actually gave him the margin of victory he needed to defeat the popular four-term governor, Wilbur Cross. Baldwin won by 2,688 votes out of some 458,000 cast. He served one term and then lost his reelection bid to Robert Hurley during the nation-wide Democratic sweep of 1940. However, two years later he challenged Hurley and was once more elected governor. He was reelected in 1944.
As governor, Baldwin established compulsory annual audits of state and town books and was able to balance the state budget without seeking new taxes. He tended to support the needs of Connecticut businesses and did not like the increased role of the Federal government under the New Deal. However, he provided a more moderate approach to government than had the Republican administrations of the 1920's.
Baldwin's accomplishments as governor were prodigious. He supported more progressive labor legislation, including an anti-injunction bill, the redefinition of conspiracy laws, greater workers' compensation benefits, and the first comprehensive pension system for state employees. He supported efforts to employ more workers in Connecticut and established a job-training program to prepare workers for defense industry jobs. This program became a model for similar programs throughout the country. In 1943 he established the Inter-Racial Commission so that grievances of the state's African-American population might be heard. This commission is believed to be the first civil rights unit of its kind in the country. He also reformed the minor court system.
Two and a half years before the US entered World War II, Baldwin reorganized the state's Military Department. He also established the State Development Commission and the Aeronautical Development Commission, two agencies that helped convert Connecticut industry from peacetime output to defense and war production. During the war, the State Defense Council was recognized as one of the foremost in the country.
In 1944 Baldwin was elected to a third term. In 1945, there was a 150-day labor strike in Connecticut. Believing it threatened national security, he used troops to stop it. During this term a state labor relations act was passed, a Connecticut Veterans Advisory and Reemployment Commission established, and a program to help equalize educational opportunities was launched.
Baldwin had planned to retire from politics when his term ended in January of 1947, but in 1946 he was convinced by his party to run for the US Senate. In order to gain seniority over other freshman senators, Baldwin resigned as governor on December 27, 1946 and went to Washington to fill the remaining term of Senator Francis T. Maloney, who had died in early January 1945. The seat had been temporarily held by Admiral Thomas C. Hart, of Sharon, Connecticut. Baldwin's resignation allowed the Democratic lieutenant governor, Wilbert Snow, to serve 13 days as governor.
Raymond Baldwin had a presence on the national Republican stage. In 1940 he was a potential running mate for Wendell Wilkie but failed to gain the nomination. In 1944 he was spoken of as potential presidential candidate. He was the Connecticut "favorite son" presidential candidate at the 1948 Republican National Convention.
In 1949, Baldwin resigned from the Senate to accept appointment by Democratic Governor Chester Bowles to the Connecticut Supreme Court of Errors. He became its Chief Justice in 1959, thereby becoming only the second Connecticut person to have served as the state's governor, US Senator, and Chief Justice (the first was Jonathan Trumbull). As Chief Justice he oversaw a major reorganization of the state's court system. After he retired from the court in 1963, Baldwin continued to work in the justice system as a referee.
He was the chairman of Connecticut's Constitutional Convention of 1965, which rewrote the state's Constitution to conform to the US Supreme Court's one-man, one-vote ruling. Baldwin was a member of the Connecticut State Library Committee and its successor, the State Library Board, from 1957-1982 and served as its chair for many years. In tribute to his service, the board renamed the State Library's museum the Raymond E. Baldwin Museum of Connecticut History in 1983. The Baldwin Bridge that carries the Connecticut Turnpike (Rt. 95) from Old Lyme to Old Saybrook is also named for him. Baldwin was the first governor to use the Governor's Mansion located on Prospect Avenue in Hartford. Two homes he once owned, one in Stratford and one in Middletown, are in private hands.
Bibliography
Baldwin, Raymond E. Let's Go Into Politics. New York: Macmillan, 1952 [CSL call number JF 2051 .B24].
Boston Sunday Globe, October 5, 1986, p. 55.
Hartford Courant, October 5, 1986, p. 1.
Johnson, Curtiss S. Raymond E. Baldwin: Connecticut Statesman. Chester, Conn.: Pequot Press, 1972 [CSL call number F 100 .B3 J6].
New York Times, October 5, 1986, p. 44.
Sobel, Robert and John Raimo. Biographical Directory of the Governors of the United States, 1789-1978. Westport, Conn.: Meckler Books, 1978 [CSL call number GIS Ref E 176 .B573].
Scope and Content
Gov. Raymond E. Baldwin's records are correspondence and subject files related to state agencies, commissions, legislative bills, and appointments among other topics. Also included are war orders.
Arrangement
Series 1. Correspondence.
Series 2. Subject Files.
Series 3. War Orders.
Series 4. Committee to Study the Medical and Hospital Service at the Connecticut Veterans Home and Hospital.
Related Material
RG 005:27, Records of the Governor, Gov. Raymond E. Baldwin, 1939-1941.
RG 006:38, Records of the Secretary of the State: Constitutional Convention of 1965.
RG 012, Records of the Connecticut State Library.
RG 040, Records of the Post-War Planning Board, 1943-1945.
RG 049, Records of the Veterans Advisory Commission, 1943-1949.
RG 050, Records of the State War Council, 1940-1945.
RG 069:10, Papers of Raymond E. Baldwin, 1938-1977. Includes records and manuscripts from his gubernatorial term up through his term as Supreme Court Justice and scrapbooks covering his entire career. Hundreds of photographs from the Baldwin family are housed with the Pictorial Archives.
Index Terms
Persons:
Baldwin, Raymond E. (Raymond Earl), 1893-1986
Subjects:
Baldwin, Raymond E. (Raymond Earl), 1893-1986 -- Archives; Connecticut. Office of the Governor -- Archives; Connecticut -- History -- Sources; Connecticut -- Politics and government -- 1865-1950 -- Sources; Governors -- Connecticut -- Archives
Document Types:
Correspondence; Executive orders; Records
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Series 1. Correspondence, 1946-10
  - A-D (Box 442)
  - E-Ka (Box 443)
  - Ke-Mo (Box 444)
  - Mu-Ri (Box 445)
  - Ro-Ti (Box 446)
  - To-Z (Box 447)
- Series 2. Subject Files, 1946-10
  - Accountancy Board (Box 448)
  - Addresses (Box 448)
    - Acceptance Speech, Bushnell Memorial Hall, Hartford, Republican State Convention, 1946 September 10 (Box 448)
    - African Dance Festival, Carnegie Hall, 1945 April 6 (Box 448)
    - American Legion Convention, Hotel Bond, Hartford, not used, 1946 August 16 (Box 448)
    - Armistice Day celebration, State Capitol, 1946 November 11 (Box 448)
    - "Bills before the general Assembly", radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 May 21 (Box 448)
    - Birthday celebration of Republic of China, Bushnell Memorial Hall, Hartford, 1944 October 10 (Box 448)
    - Board of New England Tax Officials, Hotel Bond, Hartford, 1946 October 3 (Box 448)
    - Budget, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 February 19 (Box 448)
    - California State Chamber of Commerce, 1946 December 4 (Box 448)
    - Choate School 15th Anniversary, Wallingford, Connecticut, 1946 September 27 (Box 448)
    - Closing days of the General Assembly, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 June 11 (Box 448)
    - Commencement Day, Greenwich Academy, 1945 June 2 (Box 448)
    - Commencement Exercises, St. Joseph's College, West Hartford, 1945 June 8 (Box 448)
    - Connecticut Cancer Society Drive, radio address, WDRC, Hartford, 1945 April 12 (Box 448)
    - Connecticut Cancer Society Fund, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1946 April 1 (Box 448)
    - Connecticut Federation of Labor, Hotel Bond, Hartford, 1946 September 5 (Box 448)
    - Connecticut Forum of Air 2nd Anniversary, recorded and broadcast, 1945 July 23 (Box 448)
    - Connecticut Labor Relations Act, 1945 March 26 (Box 448)
    - Connecticut Manufacturer's Association, Bushnell Memorial Hall, Hartford, 1946 October 30 (Box 448)
    - Connecticut Mutual Life Insurance Co., Community Chest Drive, 1946 October 14 (Box 448)
    - Connecticut Mutual Life Insurance Co., Hartford, 1946 June 21 (Box 448)
    - Connecticut Mutual Life Insurance Co., Atlantic City, New Jersey, 1946 June 26 (Box 448)
    - Connecticut Prison Association, Annual Luncheon, St. Joseph's College, 1945 March 21 (Box 448)
    - Connecticut Program for Veterans, radio address, WDRC, WBRY, WELI, WNLC, 6:30 p.m., 1946 April 10 (Box 448)
    - Connecticut State Bankers Association, Hotel Taft, New Haven, 1946 January 17 (Box 448)
    - Connecticut State Employees Association, Hotel Bond, Hartford, 1946 October 6 (Box 448)
    - Connecticut State Grange, Hotel Bond, Hartford, 1945 January 10 (Box 448)
    - Connecticut State Medical Society, Annual Meeting, Hartford Club, Dr. Osborn read the speech, 1946 May 2 (Box 448)
    - Connecticut State Nurses Association, Hotel Bond, Hartford, 1946 October 23 (Box 448)
    - Connecticut State Society Dinner, Hotel Statler, Washington, D.C., 1946 February 6 (Box 448)
    - Connecticut's War Program, War Council, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 April 16 (Box 448)
    - Convocation, Board of Education, State Teachers" College, New Britain, Connecticut, 1946 October 19 (Box 448)
    - Courts, Infantile paralysis drives, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 January 15 (Box 448)
    - Darien's Women Republican Club, Darien High School, Darien, Connecticut, 1946 September 18 (Box 448)
    - Demobilization Ceremony, 1945 June 16 (Box 448)
    - Factory Valley, New Haven Clock Company, New Haven, 1946 October 31 (Box 448)
    - "Farm Safety Week", "UFC", radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1946 July 22 (Box 448)
    - Fire prevention, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1946 April 8 (Box 448)
    - Fire prevention, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1946 May 1 (Box 448)
    - "Food" talk, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1946 March 25 (Box 448)
    - "Founders" Day", Lincoln, Nebraska, 1946 February 12 (Box 448)
    - Gasoline and man power, radio address, WTIC, WICC, WELI, 7:30 p.m., 1943 June 5 (Box 448)
    - Hartford County Republican Women Lunch, Hotel Bond, Hartford, 1946 October 9 (Box 448)
    - Highways, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 March 5 (Box 448)
    - Housing, New Haven Junior Chamber of Commerce, radio address, WNHC, 1946 March 11 (Box 448)
    - Infantile March of Dimes Drive, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1946 January 14 (Box 448)
    - Infantry Show, Bulkely Stadium, Hartford, 1945 June 19 (Box 448)
    - Inter-racial Scholarship Award, House of Representatives, 1945 June 19 (Box 448)
    - Latin America, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 April 9 (Box 448)
    - Legislative matters, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 May 7 (Box 448)
    - Legislative program, General Assembly, radio program, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 April 30 (Box 448)
    - Litchfield County Emergency Famine, Torrington, Connecticut, 1946 April 29 (Box 448)
    - Middlesex County Republican Women, Pease House, Saybrook, 1946 October 17 (Box 448)
    - "Neal Moylan", radio address, WTHT, 1945 November 2 (Box 448)
    - National Council of Jewish Women, Avery Memorial, radio forum, 1946 October 9 (Box 448)
    - National Maritime Day Celebration, Fort Trumbull, New London, 1945 May 22 (Box 448)
    - National Retail Dry goods Association, Hotel Pennsylvania, 1945 January 11 (Box 448)
    - National Tool and Die Manufacturers" Association, Hotel Bond, Hartford, 1946 January 25 (Box 448)
    - "Nationwide RR Strike", radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1946 May 24 (Box 448)
    - Navy Day, Hartford, 1946 October 26 (Box 448)
    - New Haven League of Women Voters, Hotel Taft, New Haven, 1946 October 28 (Box 448)
    - New Haven Women Republican Dinner, Hotel Taft, New Haven, 1946 September 16 (Box 448)
    - Newington Home for Crippled Children, 1946 October 17 (Box 448)
    - "New London Safety Award", radio address, WNLC, New London, 1946 July 11 (Box 448)
    - The Norwalk Forum, 1946 October 16 (Box 448)
    - Old Farms Convalescent Hospital, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 November 24 (Box 448)
    - "One World Dinner", Hotel Astor, New York, 1945 February 18 (Box 448)
    - Outline of Government, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 April 2 (Box 448)
    - Pan-American League, Mr. Fernando lee, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1946 April 15 (Box 448)
    - "Peace", radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 April 23 (Box 448)
    - Presentation of Navy Cross, Senate Chamber, 1945 July 11 (Box 448)
    - Prize Day, Kent School, 1945 May 30 (Box 448)
    - Rally for Colored Group, Shiloh Hall, Bridgeport, Connecticut, 1945 October 13 (Box 448)
    - 43rd Division Reactivation, Armory, 1946 October 15 (Box 448)
    - Reception for Major General Wayne, Hartford, 1945 December 1 (Box 448)
    - "Reconversion", radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 September 10 (Box 448)
    - Red Cross Rally, Bushnell Memorial Hall, Hartford, 1945 February 1 (Box 448)
    - Republican candidates for general Assembly, Putnam, Connecticut, 1946 October 18 (Box 448)
    - Republican State Central Committee, Lake Compounce, Bristol, Connecticut, 1946 July 15 (Box 448)
    - Retail President's Conference, West Middle School, Hartford, 1946 October 16 (Box 448)
    - Rochambeau Day, Old State House, Hartford, 1946 September 20 (Box 448)
    - 7th War Loan Drive, radio address, Hartford, 1945 May 14 (Box 448)
    - Situation in General Assembly, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 May 28 (Box 448)
    - Situation in General Assembly, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 June 4 (Box 448)
    - Situation in General Assembly, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1946 January 22 (Box 448)
    - Social Protection Conference, Connecticut War Council, Hartford Club, 1945 January 6 (Box 448)
    - Special Session of the General Assembly, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1946 April 22 (Box 448)
    - Special Session of the General Assembly, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1946 May 15 (Box 448)
    - State Highway Department 50th Anniversary, Senate Chambers, 1945 July 20 (Box 448)
    - Stratford Rally, 1944 October 19 (Box 448)
    - Tercentenary of New London, afternoon speech, 1946 April 30 (Box 448)
    - Traffic Safety Award Luncheon, Hartford Club, 1945 May 23 (Box 448)
    - United War Fund Meeting, Hartford, 1945 October 4 (Box 448)
    - U.S. Maritime Officers School, New London, morning, 1946 April 30 (Box 448)
    - Veterans, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 March 19 (Box 448)
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars, Hotel Taft, New Haven, 1946 October 5 (Box 448)
    - Victory Campaign, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 September 24 (Box 448)
    - WAC Medical Technicians Recruitment, 1945 March 14 (Box 448)
    - War Powers, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 February 26 (Box 448)
    - "WAVES" 3rd Anniversary, recorded broadcast, WNHC, 1945 July 25 (Box 448)
    - Welcome to station WNOC, recording, 1946 September 6 (Box 448)
    - Wildlife, Forest Parks, radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 2:45 p.m., 1946 March 2 (Box 448)
    - Windham County Republican Women, Shell Chateau, Willimantic, Connecticut, 1946 October 9 (Box 448)
    - Youth Awards Luncheon, Hotel Bond, Hartford, 1945 January 4 (Box 448)
    - American Legion, New Haven, Connecticut, 1946 October 19 (Box 448)
    - Bennett College, North Carolina, 1946 November 8 (Box 448)
    - Bloomfield College and Seminary, Bloomfield, New Jersey, 1946 November 25 (Box 448)
    - Central Baptist Church, Hartford, 1945 October 14 (Box 448)
    - Cheshire Academy, Cheshire, Connecticut, 1946 January 24 (Box 448)
    - Christ Church Forum, New York City, 1945 September 26 (Box 448)
    - Governors" Conference, Mackinac Island, Michigan, 1945 July 2 (Box 448)
    - Selective Service, State Armory, Hartford, 1946 January 21 (Box 448)
    - Radio address, WICC, Bridgeport, Connecticut, 1944 December 23 (Box 448)
    - Radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1944 October 16 (Box 448)
    - Radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1944 October 26 (Box 448)
    - Monday Nite Radio Address, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 January 8 (Box 448)
    - Monday Evening Address, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 February 5 (Box 448)
    - Radio address, WICC and WTIC, Hartford, 1945 February 12 (Box 448)
    - Radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1945 March 12 (Box 448)
    - Radio address, WDRC, Hartford, 1946 October 11 (Box 448)
    - Radio address, WDRC, Hartford, 1946 October 15 (Box 448)
    - Radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 4:30 p.m., 1946 October 20 (Box 448)
    - Radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1946 November 2 (Box 448)
    - Radio address, WTIC, Hartford, 1946 November 4 (Box 448)
    - Radio address, WDRC, Hartford, 1946 November 4 (Box 448)
    - Radio address, WNLC, New London, Connecticut, 1946 October 25 (Box 448)
    - Radio address, WSRR, Stamford, Connecticut, 1944 October 27 (Box 448)
    - Radio address, WSTC, Stamford, Connecticut, 1944 October 24 (Box 448)
    - Radio address, WSTC, Stamford, Connecticut, 1944 October 26 (Box 448)
    - Radio address, WWCO, Waterbury, Connecticut, 1944 October 29 (Box 449)
    - Republican Campaign radio address, Torrington, 1944 November 1 (Box 449)
    - Republican Campaign radio address, WNLC, New London, Connecticut, 1944 November 2 (Box 449)
    - Republican Campaign radio address by Gov. Baldwin, WTIC, Hartford, 1944 November 5 (Box 449)
    - Republican Campaign radio address, Saltonstall, Edge, and Senator Austin, WNBC, 1944 November 5 (Box 449)
    - Address by Herbert Hoover, "The San Francisco Charter and the Progress toward Enduring Peace" (Box 449)
    - Address by Gov. Herbert R. O'Connor, Salisbury Rotary Club, Wicomico Hotel, 1945 August 16 (Box 449)
    - Address by Lt. Gov. Wilbert Snow, "To the Marines," Hall of Flags, State Capitol, 1946 August 30 (Box 449)
    - Address by Harold E. Stassen, Republican State Convention, Bushnell Memorial Hall, Hartford, Connecticut, 1946 September 9 (Box 449)
  - Adjutant General, 2 folders (Box 449)
  - Advisory Board on Aeronautics (Box 449)
  - Advisory Committee, Institute of Labor and Management Relations (Box 449)
  - Advisory Council for State Employees (Box 449)
  - Advisory Highway Commission (Box 449)
  - Advisory Personnel Committee (Box 449)
  - Aeronautics Commission (Box 449)
  - Aeronautics Department (Box 449)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station (Box 449)
  - Agriculture Department (Box 449)
  - Airport Meeting Luncheon Hartford Times - Mr. Murphy (Box 449)
  - Air Transport (Box 449)
  - Alcohol Control (Box 449)
  - American Academy of Political and Social Science (Box 449)
  - American Palestine Committee (Box 449)
  - American School for the Deaf (Box 449)
  - Apprenticeship Council (Box 450)
  - Appropriations (Box 450)
  - Arbor Day (Box 450)
  - Architectural Examining Board (Box 450)
  - Army Exhibit State Armory July 10, 11, 12, 13, 1946 (Box 450)
  - Athletic Commissioner (Box 450)
  - Atlantic States Marine Fisheries Commission (Box 450)
  - Attorney General (Box 450)
  - Auditing Department (Box 450)
  - Aviation Legislation - Governors' Conference - Correspondence with Frank Bane (Box 450)
  - Aviation - Meeting of January 8, 1945, Hartford, Conn. (Box 450)
  - Avon Old Farms School (School for Blind Veterans) (Box 450)
  - Banking - Credit Pools (Box 450)
  - Banking Department (Box 450)
  - Barber Examiners (Box 450)
  - Battleship Connecticut (Box 450)
  - Beach Erosion (Box 450)
  - Blood Plasma Bank (Box 450)
  - Board of Chiropractic Examiners (Box 450)
  - Board of Education for the Blind (Box 450)
  - Board of Examiners of Embalmers (Box 450)
  - Board of Examiners for Physiotherapy Technicians (Box 450)
  - Board of Examiners of Psychologists (Box 450)
  - Board of Natureopathic Examiners (Box 450)
  - Board of Osteopathic Registration and Examination (Box 450)
  - Board of Pardons (Box 450)
  - Board of Professional Engineers and Land Surveyors (Box 450)
  - Board of Supervision of Dams (Box 450)
  - Bradley Field (Box 450)
  - Branford Town Court Judgeship (Box 450)
  - Bridgeport Police Situation (Box 450)
  - Budget Division (Box 450)
  - Budget Hearings (Box 450)
  - Budget Message (Box 450)
  - Cancer Drive (Box 451)
  - Celebration, 102nd Inf. (Box 451)
  - Celebrities in Conn., List of (Box 451)
  - Census Bureau (Box 451)
  - Central Labor Council (New Haven) (Box 451)